struggling to keep up with school work
what if i do i do there's
there's a small assistant that can meet student
student life easier boost your dreams
dreams i'm talking about the
the i to is not cheating
cheating learning smarter
these are just for deck experts
they're genuinely useful for every student
student first facing
facing dense text books the
the i judge gp can summarize
summarize complex articles seconds willing
willing out keep going grasp insects
insects faster second
staring at a blank page for an essay
use a high as a brainstorming
brainstorming buddy as get
get to generate need ages are two basic
basic outline to kickstart you're thinking
third a for concept
isn't flicking as a i had to explain
explain it in simpler terms give examples
examples or even with
a ducks to your learning stein
morning to save time get better
better results your action
today pick one assignment enjoy using
using an ailing too ill to summarize antarctic
antarctic in you'll love it